<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<layouts>
    <layout type="article-set" subtype="tall-large-right" priority="high">
        <article titleSize="huge" imgLayout="tall">
            <url>elder-scrolls-online</url>
            <tag>elder-scrolls-online</tag>
            <count>01-main.png</count>
            <subtype>review</subtype>
            <title>The Elder Scrolls Online</title>
            <symbols>340</symbols>
            <content>
                <![CDATA[<p>Presentation matters more the longer you plan to
                    spend in a game world, and The Elder Scrolls Online demands
                    a tremendous amount of your time. It feels like an MMOG from
                    several years ago, an artefact of a time when players expected
                    to invest hundreds of hours to reach a level cap and an MMOG
                    wasn’t just a new game to dabble in but a new world to occupy.
                    The game’s pace is glacial, and your progression as a player
                    painstaking, incremental. Where most recent games in this
                    genre trip over themselves to provide a sense of impact and
                    achievement, TESO hopes you’ll settle for some slightly more
                    elaborately embossed shoulder pads.</p>]]>
            </content>
        </article>
        <article imgLayout="large">
            <url>still-playing-titanfall</url>
            <tag>titanfall</tag>
            <count>01-main.png</count>
            <subtype>feature</subtype>
            <title>Still Playing: Titanfall – why endlessly rewarding players
                is not endlessly rewarding</title>
            <content>
                <![CDATA[<p>Shooters are the ultimate videogame power fantasy:
                    a man and a gun fighting through a string of life-or-death
                    encounters with the heart-in-mouth tension of war but none
                    of the risk. Yet the online FPS’s sparse traditional framework
                    – a winner, a loser and a scoreboard – naturally limits its
                    own longevity. The object of the game never changes, its
                    systems stay fixed in place, and you’re as powerful when
                    you set foot on the battlefield as when you leave it. The
                    thrill wears off.</p>]]>
            </content>
        </article>
    </layout>
    <layout type="video-set" priority="high">
        <article imgLayout="large" priority="high" isVideo="video" player="1">
            <tag>unreal-engine-4</tag>
            <count>01-main.png</count>
            <subtype>video</subtype>
            <title>The Imagination Engine: Why next-gen videogames will rock
                your world</title>
            <url>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dD9CPqSKjTU</url>
        </article>
        <article imgLayout="small" priority="high" isVideo="video" player="1">
            <tag>dark-souls-2</tag>
            <count>01-main.png</count>
            <subtype>video</subtype>
            <title>Darks Souls 2 видео ревю</title>
            <url>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=t44khNV1b5M</url>
        </article>
        <article imgLayout="small" priority="high" isVideo="video" isLast="last" player="1">
            <tag>game-of-thrones-4</tag>
            <count>01-main.png</count>
            <subtype>video</subtype>
            <title>Game of Thrones сезон 4: зад кулисите</title>
            <url>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jf6oDup2VGA</url>
        </article>
    </layout>
    <layout type="article-set" subtype="small-set-caret-left" priority="medium">
        <article titleSize="big" imgLayout="tall" isCaret="caret">
            <url>the-amazing-spiderman-2</url>
            <tag>the-amazing-spiderman-2</tag>
            <count>01-main.png</count>
            <subtype>news</subtype>
            <title>The Amazing Spider-Man 2</title>
            <symbols>416</symbols>
            <content>
                <![CDATA[<p>We've always known that Spider-Man'sWe've always
                    known that Spider-Man's most important battle has been within
                    himself: the struggle between the ordinary obligations of
                    Peter Parker and the extraordinary responsibilities of Spider-Man.
                    But in The Amazing Spider-Man 2, Peter Parker finds that
                    a greater conflict lies ahead. It's great to be Spider-Man
                    (Andrew Garfield). For Peter Parker, there's no feeling quite
                    like swinging between skyscrapers, embracing being the hero,
                    and spending time with Gwen (Emma Stone). But being Spider-Man
                    comes at a price: only Spider-Man can protect his fellow
                    New Yorkers from the formidable villains that threaten the
                    city. With the emergence of Electro (Jamie Foxx), Peter must
                    confront a foe far more powerful than he. And as his old
                    friend, Harry Osborn (Dane DeHaan), returns, Peter comes
                    to realize that all of his enemies have one thing in common:
                    OsCorp. (c) Columbia.</p>]]>
            </content>
        </article>
        <article imgLayout="small">
            <url>captain-america-2014</url>
            <tag>captain-america-2014</tag>
            <count>01-main.png</count>
            <subtype>review</subtype>
            <title>Captain America: The Winter Soldier</title>
            <symbols>0</symbols>
            <content>
                <![CDATA[<p>Bloated and shallow as they are, comic-book-superhero
                    pictures can occasionally surprise you. Imagine looking back
                    on this decade, the dawn of the age of weaponized surveillance
                    drones, and finding that the only harbingers of what was
                    to come were the (middling) remake of RoboCop and Captain
                    America: The Winter Soldier. Beneath the expensive, computer-generated
                    busyness of this second Captain America installment is a
                    bracing, old-style conspiracy thriller made extra-scary by
                    new technology and the increasingly ugly trade-offs of a
                    post-9/11 world.</p>]]>
            </content>
        </article>
        <article imgLayout="small">
            <url>making-of-mario-3d</url>
            <tag>making-of-mario-3d</tag>
            <count>01-main.png</count>
            <subtype>feature</subtype>
            <title>The Making Of: Super Mario 3D World</title>
            <symbols>736</symbols>
            <content>
                <![CDATA[<p>No tea tables were upended – as a Nintendo euphemism
                    for radical changes towards the end of a game’s development
                    goes – during the making of Super Mario 3D World. Since 2005’s
                    Donkey Kong Jungle Beat, Nintendo EAD Tokyo has blossomed
                    into one of the publisher’s finest assets, and it says much
                    for the regard with which the group is held that Shigeru
                    Miyamoto and fellow Nintendo veteran Takashi Tezuka felt
                    comfortable taking a back seat, their responsibilities limited
                    to "occasional spot checks". The two designers of the original
                    Super Mario Bros could rest easy: their most famous creation
                    was in safe hands.</p>]]>
            </content>
        </article>
    </layout>
</layouts>
