<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<layouts>
    <layout type="read-set">
        <left>
            <article imgLayout="tall" isAdvert="advert">
                <tag>diablo-3-reaper-of-souls</tag>
                <subtype>info</subtype>
                <info box="win">
                    <bg>Караконяк 3: Комбайнер на Души</bg>
                    <en>Diablo 3: Reaper of Souls</en>
                    <platform>
                        <tag>Win</tag>
                        <tag>Mac</tag>
                        <tag>PS4</tag>
                        <tag>One</tag>
                        <tag>PS3</tag>
                        <tag>360</tag>
                    </platform>
                    <publisher>Blizzard Entertainment</publisher>
                    <developer>Blizzard Entertainment</developer>
                    <eu>25 Март 2014</eu>
					<usa>25 Март 2014</usa>
                </info>
                <advert>
                    <button>Купи Играта</button>
                    <tag>pulsar</tag>
                </advert>
            </article>
        </left>
        <right>
            <article titleSize="big" imgLayout="tall" isCaret="caret">
                <tag>diablo-3</tag>
                <count>01-main.png</count>
                <subtype>review</subtype>
                <title>Диабло 3</title>
                <symbols>0</symbols>
                <content>
                    <![CDATA[<p>Diablo III benefits from great writing. Not necessarily
                        in the narrative or dialogue, both of which offer the
                        same old gleefully stagey stuff about warring angels
                        and ancient prophecies. No, it has great writing where
                        it matters: in the names of its class skills. Wrath Of
                        The Berserker, Rain Of Vengeance, Mass Confusion – here’s
                        where creative effort has been spent. Here’s where you
                        can see the density of pulpy exuberance that ten years
                        of development can provide.</p>]]>
                </content>
            </article>
        </right>
        <content>
            <![CDATA[<p>I can’t recall a gaming villain who looks as imposing
                as Reaper of Souls’ Malthael but leaves so weak an impression.
                He pops in and out as the narrative unfolds, spouting a few threatening
                lines before evaporating in a mist of gloom, and thus he recalls
                Blizzard's similar treatment of Arthas Menethil during World
                of Warcraft's Wrath of the Lich King expansion. But at least
                Arthas had the benefit of years of accumulated lore to support
                his cameos. The star of but one act, Malthael is never around
                long enough to make us care about his grumbles.</p><p>Malthael's
                saga delivers few surprises; there's little like the shifting
                allegiances and unexpected deaths of Diablo III proper. If it
                warrants attention at all, it's only in that it lets us settle
                a score gone unpunished from the first outing (and in the weakest
                of the expansion's three boss fights, no less). Instead, it's
                the environment that stands out in Reaper of Souls. As if in
                defiance of criticisms that Diablo III was too soft, Blizzard
                kicks off its tale with medieval streets paved with bodies that
                squish under your feet. Later, marshlands simmer with more menace
                than I ever felt in the Leoric Highlands or Dalghur Oasis, and
                the portal-ridden citadel of Pandemonium mirrors Malthael’s madness.
                Reaper of Souls fails to serve a sufficiently epic story, but
                it nails the ambiance.</p><q>The console release goes further
                in its streamlining, making item drops rarer and more useful
                across the board.</q><p>The cast is as entertaining as Reaper’s
                setting, too, with demon dogs that wriggle you in their jaws
                like a squeaky toy and a boss that wields a demonic flamethrower
                while a burning ceiling collapses around him. Perhaps that's
                why Blizzard's kept the prattling to a minimum: story never gets
                in the way of Reaper’s eternal hunt for the next best loot upgrade
                or its satisfyingly responsive dance of combat and movement.
                Instead of force-feeding us tragedies, Blizzard instead invests
                in spectacle. Malthael himself makes up for his insipid tale
                with a fantastic boss fight that makes Diablo’s feel like a glittery
                piñata bash.</p><p>At times, I felt as though I should reach
                for popcorn. Am I really battling on top of a moving battering
                ram in Pandemonum? Thank the heavens, I am.</p>]]>
        </content>
    </layout>
    <layout type="img-set" subtype="1a">
        <img isImg="img" size="medium" isExtended="extended">
            <tag>diablo-3-reaper-of-souls</tag>
            <count>07-640.png</count>
            <pointer>Горе</pointer>
            <content>
                <![CDATA[Уменията на всеки паладин в мятането на чукове и боя
                    със светещи юмруци са науспорими, но най-страховитото си
                    остава отвличането с НЛО.]]>
            </content>
        </img>
        <img isImg="img" size="small" isExtended="extended">
            <tag>diablo-3-reaper-of-souls</tag>
            <count>08-640.png</count>
            <pointer>Дясно</pointer>
            <content>
                <![CDATA[Крусейдърът труда обича, на помощ първи се притича.]]>
            </content>
        </img>
        <img isImg="img" size="large" isExtended="extended" playVideo="video" player="1">
            <tag>diablo-3-reaper-of-souls</tag>
            <count>04.png</count>
            <pointer>Ляво</pointer>
            <title>Видео ревю</title>
            <url>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9Wpqop0bGZQ</url>
            <content>
                <![CDATA[Основните ценности на всеки свещен войн: бой, дюлева
                    ракия и сръбска музика.]]>
            </content>
        </img>
    </layout>
    <layout type="read-set">
        <left>
            <article isQ="q" qImg="deckard-cain.png">
                <author>Deckard Cain</author>
                <title>Hello, my friend. Stay awhile and listen.</title>
            </article>
        </left>
        <right>
            <article imgLayout="small">
                <tag>diablo-3-reaper-of-souls</tag>
                <count>02.png</count>
                <subtype>video</subtype>
                <title>
                    <![CDATA[Комбайнер на Души<br /> начално филмче]]>
                </title>
                <symbols>0</symbols>
                <content>
                    <![CDATA[<p>The End of Days has begun:<br /><a target="_blank"
                        href="http://diablo3.com/ReaperOfSouls">http://diablo3.com/ReaperOfSouls</a>
                        <br /> The next chapter in Sanctuary's epic saga has
                        been unveiled. Originally debuted at gamescom 2013 on
                        August 21 in Cologne, Germany, this is the opening cinematic
                        for Diablo III's first expansion set, Reaper of Souls.
                        For all the latest news and information regarding this
                        major update to the critically acclaimed Diablo franchise,
                        visit:<br /><a target="_blank" href="http://www.diablo3.com">http://www.diablo3.com</a>
                        </p>]]>
                </content>
            </article>
        </right>
        <content>
            <![CDATA[<h3>Play it again, Sam(ael)</h3><p>I’m especially pleased
                by the direction Blizzard took Reaper’s levels because there
                were sections of Diablo III that I dreaded slogging through&mdash;zones
                like High Heavens with their bland grandeur&mdash;but each of
                Reaper’s eleven zones here yields its own treats. What's more,
                some levels shift randomly with each new playthrough so you're
                never running through the same map twice. Randomized events pop
                up around most grimy corners. Some of these rely on familiar
                scenarios like fending off hordes on a timer, but others present
                vignettes that demand attention. One time I stepped through an
                unassuming door and found a would-be usurper gloating over the
                slain leader of Westmarch. And when my haughty Crusader condemned
                him for taking advantage of the chaos to further his own ambition,
                I felt his zeal.</p><p>He was a tough bastard, but only because
                I allowed it. The massive patch that dropped two weeks before
                launch let all players choose specific difficulty modes at their
                leisure, and this mattered a great deal for my well-geared level
                60 character with a 55 Paragon rating. For around two years,
                you could only reach the tough stuff by chugging through three
                separate difficulty modes corresponding to fixed level brackets
                across three playthroughs. The “hardest,” Inferno, was sometimes
                stupidly easy thanks to its fixed nature and the conveniences
                of gear optimization from the auction house. About a month ago
                I jumped into a multiplayer battle on Inferno mode with Azmodan,
                the boss of Diablo III's third act, and saw him three-shotted
                by a high-level, well-geared Paragon.</p><p>Reaper of Souls may
                give folks like him a hard time. Without the tiresome need to
                slog through an overly easy first playthrough to access tougher
                stuff; I could choose from one of five difficulty settings right
                from the beginning and change them if it got too rough. But wait,
                it gets better. Select the highest level difficulty, "Torment,"
                and you'll find a slider that lets you bump it up six additional
                tiers of brutality. That gives you perks like 300 percent extra
                gold or 300 percent extra XP, but if you're unprepared like I
                was, it'll knock you silly. Weeks or months from now, when I’m
                decked out in the godliest of gear, I’ll be grateful for the
                remaining challenges and associated replay value.</p>]]>
        </content>
    </layout>
    <layout type="img-set" subtype="2a">
        <img isImg="img" size="large" isExtended="extended">
            <tag>diablo-3-reaper-of-souls</tag>
            <count>11.png</count>
            <pointer>Ляво</pointer>
            <content>
                <![CDATA[Мосфильм представя битката на хилядолетието: крусейдър
                    с гигантски чук напада двусърп арахангел в кулата на Кремъл.]]>
            </content>
        </img>
        <img isImg="img" size="medium" isExtended="extended" playVideo="video" player="2">
            <tag>diablo-3-reaper-of-souls</tag>
            <count>12-1280.png</count>
            <pointer>Долу</pointer>
            <url>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hTziAabfVEw</url>
            <content>
                <![CDATA[Дърт Тириел млада енхантреса лющеше па си на главен
                    герой думаше - още 4 куки и та почвам и тебе ма пача.]]>
            </content>
        </img>
        <img isImg="img" size="small" isExtended="extended">
            <tag>diablo-3-reaper-of-souls</tag>
            <count>10-640.png</count>
            <pointer>Горе</pointer>
            <content>
                <![CDATA[Засукан магьосник, гали светеща топка, а на заден план
                    от черна дупка се задава още по-черен к... ураган.]]>
            </content>
        </img>
    </layout>
    <layout type="read-set">
        <left>
            <article isQ="q" qImg="malthael.png">
                <author>Malthael</author>
                <title>No-one can stop death...</title>
            </article>
        </left>
        <right>
            <article imgLayout="small">
                <tag>diablo-3-reaper-of-souls</tag>
                <count>01.png</count>
                <subtype>aside</subtype>
                <title>
                    <![CDATA[New Experience<br /><br />]]>
                </title>
                <symbols>0</symbols>
                <content>
                    <![CDATA[<p>Diablo 3's post-cap experience system has been
                        rebooted for Loot 2.0 and Reaper of Souls. The Paragon
                        system now applies account wide — meaning every character
                        regardless of their base level reaps the benefits of
                        paragon experience. As you gain paragon levels, you assign
                        a point in one of four categories. This adds small bonuses
                        to higher level characters, but the real change can be
                        felt with lower-level alts - the changed system makes
                        it much easier to play new characters and level them
                        up faster, and play more challenging difficulties sooner.</p>]]>
                </content>
            </article>
        </right>
        <content>
            <![CDATA[<h3>Bible thumper</h3><p>The Crusader class is a worthy
                addition. He’s a likeable fellow that sounds a lot like Iain
                Glen in the role of Ser Jorah Mormont on HBO's Game of Thrones,
                and despite his (or her) fervor, he's not a caricature like the
                Templar. I've never really been one for Paladin-style classes,
                but the Crusader sold me. Here Blizzard gives us a badass that
                can wield two-handed weapons in one hand and a shield in another,
                and he shoots a fiery shield across the room as though he were
                the Vatican's take on Captain America. Press one key, and he
                summons a flaming steed that heals him, tramples enemies, or
                drags them behind him; press another, and he soars up and crashes
                down in a holy shockwave. I initially worried that some of his
                skills mirror the comparatively humble Barbarian's too closely:
                the “Akarat's Champion” ability, for instance, is essentially
                just a reskinned Wrath of the Berserker. But had I not played
                a Barbarian for countless hours in the months leading up to Reaper’s
                release, I probably wouldn’t have noticed. He’s fun, to the point
                that the older classes sometimes feel like rough drafts.</p>
                <p>And yes, to acknowledge the elephant in the room, the swappable
                skill system remains much the same. Sorry, Path of Exile fans.
                (And yes, Diablo III is still an always-online game, although
                Reaper launched with none of the connection issues that hounded
                the first release and spawned their own meme.) But Blizzard focuses
                on letting us play the way we want to play in other ways besides
                skill trees, most notably in the form of the new the Adventure
                Mode and Nephalem Rifts, both of which shatter the grinding linearity
                of battling through the same levels in sequence ad infinitum.</p>
                <q>Nephalem Rifts, which drop randomly in Adventure Mode mode,
                draw from the entire game's assets to push Reaper of Souls' emphasis
                on randomness to the extreme.</q><p>Adventure Mode is almost
                rebellious in its freedom: it lets you access all five acts (even
                if you haven't played them) and battle through them with level-appropriate
                enemies at your leisure. It’s strong enough to justify Reaper
                of Souls’ otherwise steep asking price on its own. Nephalem Rifts,
                which drop randomly in Adventure Mode mode, draw from the entire
                game's assets to push Reaper of Souls' emphasis on randomness
                to the extreme. In one of my favorite examples, I battled gigantic
                Withermoths from Act I within 10 levels of corridors from Bastion's
                Keep from Act III. In light of such dizzying variety, the campaign
                feels secondary and almost unnecessary. It's a smart design that
                encourages both extended solo and multiplayer play; whatever
                you want to do, there's a good chance you can do it.</p><p>Still
                other features enhance the experience. The new Transmogrification
                system, a World of Warcraft import, ensured that my Crusader
                always looked rightfully awesome by letting him adopt the look
                of preset models or Reaper’s legendaries. A new Mystic NPC that
                lets you swap out a single stat on an item for a randomized new
                stat fills some of the void left by the auction house, but high
                resource costs and randomization seem to keep any exploitation
                in check. All of this combines to make Diablo III both an apology
                and a love letter, the game it should have been all along.</p>
                <p>There may be more to come. Approaching the doors leading to
                Malthael, the Templar asks the Crusader, "What happens after
                Malthael is dead?" The Crusader, ever stoic, replies: "There
                will always be more evil to face. I expect to die fighting it."</p>
                <p>If Blizzard keeps this up, I expect to be there with him.</p>]]>
        </content>
    </layout>
</layouts>
