<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<layouts>
    <layout type="read-set">
        <left>
            <article titleSize="big" imgLayout="small" isCaret="caret">
                <tag>advert</tag>
                <count>01-eventim-main.png</count>
                <subtype>aside</subtype>
                <symbols>0</symbols>
                <advert>
                    <button>Купи Билети</button>
                </advert>
                <content>
                    <![CDATA[<p>The 15th edition of the best European festival
                        is going to be EXIT ADVENTURE that encompasses ROCK@EXIT
                        on 11th June - an additional one day prequel festival
                        headlined by Queens of the Stone Age.<br />Then the EXIT
                        festival, held from 10th to 13th July 2014 at the Petrovaradin
                        fortress in Novi Sad, all lastly the SEA DANCE FESTIVAL
                        from 15th to 17th July at the Jaz beach, one the most
                        stunning beaches of Adriatic.</p>]]>
                </content>
            </article>
        </left>
        <right>
            <article titleSize="big" imgLayout="small" isCaret="caret">
                <tag>advert</tag>
                <count>01-tuborg-main.png</count>
                <subtype>aside</subtype>
                <title>EXIT Label</title>
                <symbols>0</symbols>
                <content>
                    <![CDATA[<p>The website <a href="http://exitmusic.rs/en">exitmusic.rs/en</a>
                        was created in February 2009 with a desire to offer local
                        and regional performers better promotion through free
                        downloads and live performances on the festival. Exit
                        provides talented musicians with systematic support,
                        using its existing logistics and promotional campaigns.
                        In five years, Exit online label has released 50 LPs
                        and EPs available for free download, with more than 2
                        million downloads.</p>]]>
                </content>
            </article>
        </right>
        <content>
            <![CDATA[<p>EXIT, the best European festival, is a summer music festival
                held every July for four days at the Petrovaradin Fortress in
                Novi Sad, Serbia. EXIT’s key stages are the Main Stage, Dance
                Arena, Fusion, Explosive, Reggae Stage, accompanied by various
                smaller ones. The Exit festival was founded in 2000, as a student
                movement, fighting for freedom and democracy in Serbia.</p><q>The
                best European festival!</q><p>Exit won the "Best Major European
                Festival Award" on European Festival Awards 2013 with the help
                of 620 000 votes all over the world, all the while facing stiff
                competition from over 300 festivals in 34 ccountries; it won
                the "Best European Festival" award at the UK Festival Awards
                in 2007,and was ranked one of the 10 best major festivals at
                European Festival Awards 2009, 2010, 2011 and 2012 and one of
                the 10 Best Overseas Festival at UK Festival Awards 2013.</p>
                <p>More than 2,5 milllion people from over 60 countries around
                the world have visited the festival so far. Known for its incredible
                atmosphere, and one of the best Dance Arenas in the world and
                unique location, it offers visitors the most exciting, versatile
                summer adventure. During 4 days there are from 150 to 200 000
                visitors, of which there are at least 23 000 foreign tourists
                and 7000 visitors from the Balkans.</p><q>The craziest summer
                adventure!</q><p>Get ready for a spectacular summer adventure
                that's packed with two of the hottest destinations this year
                - the Petrovaradin fortress and the mesmerizing Jaz beach! Pack
                your things, and get your friends and embark on an adventure!
                Imagine a vacation filled with awesome parties at night and soothing
                sunshine and sea waves by day! You'll go back home with loads
                of great stories to tell!</p><p>The 15th edition of the best
                European festival is going to be EXIT ADVENTURE that encompasses
                ROCK@EXIT on 11th June - an additional one day prequel festival
                headlined by Queens of the Stone Age - then the EXIT festival,
                held from 10th to 13th July 2014 at the Petrovaradin fortress
                in Novi Sad, all lastly the SEA DANCE FESTIVAL from 15th to 17th
                July at the Jaz beach, one the most stunning beaches of Adriatic.</p><h3>Incredible
                2014 ADVENTURE lineup!</h3><p>This year's lineup has the hottest
                acts exclusively playing at EXIT festival - most of whom have
                concerts for the first time in the region!</p>]]>
        </content>
    </layout>
    <layout type="img-set" subtype="3a">
        <img isImg="img" size="small">
            <tag>exit-2014</tag>
            <count>01-640.png</count>
            <pointer>Damon Albarn</pointer>
            <content>
                <![CDATA[Blur i Gorillaz foudner, the must-not-miss headliner
                    at Europe's best festivals this year.]]>
            </content>
        </img>
        <img isImg="img" size="small">
            <tag>exit-2014</tag>
            <count>02-640.png</count>
            <pointer>Rudimental</pointer>
            <content>
                <![CDATA[The best new band, as voted by the world audience at
                    UK Festival Awards!]]>
            </content>
        </img>
        <img isImg="img" size="small">
            <tag>exit-2014</tag>
            <count>03-640.png</count>
            <pointer>Skrillex, Afrojack, Carl Cox</pointer>
            <content>
                <![CDATA[An explosive cocktail of a dubstep king, a DJ like you
                    haven't seen before, and the father of house and host of
                    the most incredible parties worldwide.]]>
            </content>
        </img>
        <img isImg="img" size="small">
            <tag>exit-2014</tag>
            <count>04-640.png</count>
            <pointer>Suede</pointer>
            <content>
                <![CDATA[Founders of brit pop, the music genre paved later by
                    Oasis and Blur, are excklusively coming to EXIT, for the
                    first time in the region!]]>
            </content>
        </img>
        <img isImg="img" size="small">
            <tag>exit-2014</tag>
            <count>05-640.png</count>
            <pointer>Hurts</pointer>
            <content>
                <![CDATA[Best festival band, voted by the audience of Glastonbury
                    as BEST PERFORMANCE when faced with stiff competition from
                    Coldplay, U2, Beyoncee, and more.]]>
            </content>
        </img>
        <img isImg="img" size="small">
            <tag>exit-2014</tag>
            <count>06-640.png</count>
            <pointer>Gloria Gaynor</pointer>
            <content>
                <![CDATA[Main Stage becomes the place of music history as we
                    listen to I Will Survive live!]]>
            </content>
        </img>
        <img isImg="img" size="small">
            <tag>exit-2014</tag>
            <count>07-640.png</count>
            <pointer>Pet Shop Boys, Es Davlin</pointer>
            <content>
                <![CDATA[PSB bring with them the incredible Es Devlin for an
                    out-of-this-world EXIT opening ceremony - it's not a concert,
                    it's a musical, a show, a new art form!]]>
            </content>
        </img>
        <img isImg="img" size="small">
            <tag>exit-2014</tag>
            <count>08-640.png</count>
            <pointer>Stromae</pointer>
            <content>
                <![CDATA[The legendary hit maker, with over half a billion views
                    on YouTube, will play his incredibly catchy songs Alors on
                    Dance, Papaoutai, Formidable and many more!]]>
            </content>
        </img>
    </layout>
    <layout type="read-set">
        <content>
            <![CDATA[<h3>Sea Dance Festival</h3><p>As a special treat for the
                15th edition of the EXIT festival, the SEA DANCE FESTIVAL represents
                an extension of the original 4 days of EXIT, to be held from
                15th to 17th July, as an additional 3 intense days of music and
                performances, to be held at the beautiful Jaz beach in Montenegro,
                near Budva.</p> <p>SEA DANCE is must-visit for all fans for all
                die-hard fans of electro music coupled with the sounds of the
                sea, the sun’s warm kiss, and soft sand beneath their feet. Would
                you like to go on an epic adventure and have a blast with your
                mates at heaven on earth - day parties at the hottest beach of
                the Adriatic Sea, beautiful sunsets with some of the best electro
                beats and cocktail parties on the beach?</p><q>Are you ready
                for the craziest summer beach party?</q><p>Located at the mesmerizing
                Adriatic Sea coast, SEA DANCE will present favourite EXIT stages
                and countless world, music and regional stars. Apart from <strong>MAIN
                STAGE</strong> and its 30000 attendee capacity, Sea Dance also
                boasts <strong>DANCE PARADISE, REGGAE STAGE, SILENT DANCE, LATINO
                STAGE, CINEMA and CHILL ZONE</strong></p><p>The sea edition of
                EXIT will be marked by some of the hottest contemporary stars.
                The first night is slated for <strong>Jamiroquai</strong>, helmed
                by the extravagant singer Jay Kay, who’ll get 30 000 people dirty
                dancing to some funky tunes. The star of the second evening will
                be the mega popular <strong>Example</strong>, author of "Changed
                the Way You Kiss Me" who’s also going to premiere his new album
                exclusively at Jaz. The festival will close to the furious rhythm
                of <strong>Underworld</strong>, one of the greatest ensembles
                in electro music history.</p><p>Along with the aforementioned,
                there’s also going to be tons of world and regional stars like
                <strong>Klingande, Juan Atkins, Timo Maas, Roger Sanchez, Patife,
                Mirk Knight, Bad Copy, Darkwood Dub, Eddy Temple-Morris, Eyesburn,
                Lollobridgida, Kiril Djaikovski ft. TK Wonder</strong> and many
                others!</p><p>How would you like to go on an adventure of a lifetime?</p>]]>
        </content>
    </layout>
    <layout type="img-set" subtype="4a">
        <img isImg="img" size="large" isCaret="caret">
            <tag>exit-2014</tag>
            <count>03.png</count>
            <content>
                <![CDATA[<h3>Quick Facts - Quicker than Marvel’s Flash</h3><p>The
                    website <a href="http://exitmusic.rs/en">exitmusic.rs/en</a>
                    was created in February 2009 with a desire to offer local
                    and regional performers better promotion through free downloads
                    and live performances on the festival. Exit provides talented
                    musicians with systematic support, using its existing logistics
                    and promotional campaigns. In five years, Exit online label
                    has released 50 LPs and EPs available for free download,
                    with more than 2 million downloads.</p><p>EXIT Festival 2014
                    takes place from 10th to 13th July. It lasts for four incredible,
                    intense days during the smooth summer of a continental climate.
                    The biggest stages are Main Stage, Dance Arena, Fusion Stage,
                    Reggae Stage, with more smaller, more intimate ones, that
                    change their name and location each year. The Main Stage’s
                    capacity is about 25 000, and Dance Arena can hold about
                    20 000 visitors.<br /><a href="http://www.exitfest.org/en/lineup/lineup-2014/">See
                    the current band list.</a></p> <p>The country’s capital Belgrade
                    is about 94 kilometres away from Novi Sad (about an hour
                    and a half drive) and is close to the Nikola Tesla Airport.<br
                    /><a href="http://www.exittrip.org/eng/">See practical travel
                    info at our EXIT TRIP page.</a></p><p>EXIT’s been held for
                    14 years now (Founded in 2000). Over the years, EXIT organization
                    has also welcomed names such as Red Hot Chilly Peppers, The
                    Prodigy, Depeche Mode, Billy Idol, Madonna, Nick Cave, Moby,
                    David Guetta and many more, who performed in Serbia in organization
                    of the Exit team.</p>]]>
            </content>
        </img>
    </layout>
    <layout type="read-set">
        <content>
            <![CDATA[<h3>Our History</h3><p>The Exit festival was founded in
                2000 as a student movement, so as to fight for freedom and democracy
                in Serbia. It was the first place youth gathered at from all
                former Yugoslav republics after a decade of civil wars.<br />The
                end of a decade long melancholy and apathy began with the first
                democratic elections, at the bank of the Danube river near the
                University campus, when for 100 days and nights young visitors
                counted down the days until the end of Milošević’s reign. During
                those 100 days there were 34 big concerts where the biggest bands
                in the country played, 12 theater plays, over 120 film projections
                (some were premiered in Novi Sad), 20 discussion panels, 40 huge
                parties, and 11 performances. The last concert was held on 22nd
                September 2000, two days before the election, with the message
                “He’s done” spread in front of 20.000 visitors. EXIT symbolically
                presented an exit out of decades of insanity.</p><p>EXIT then
                relocated next year to the other side of the Danube, at the Petrovaradin
                fortress. The festival was held from 6th to 14th in 2001 and
                was the first year when EXIT became a full fledged music festival
                of european calibre, which only continued to grow and improve
                in the following years.</p><p>After centuries of turbulent history,
                the Petrovaradin fortress is on the list of protected monuments
                as a historical, cultural and artistic center of Novi Sad. On
                the opposite side of the river, a magnificent view stretches
                over the second biggest Serbian city, Novi Sad, founded in 1694.
                During the long history of the city, the multicultural identity
                of the city has been maintained. Today, Novi Sad is the industrial
                and financial center of The Republic of Serbia’s economy, and
                also a cultural capital of Vojvodina. Picturesque Novi Sad has
                a lot to offer to its visitors. Besides rich history, the city
                is known for its splendid nightlife, amazing restaurant offers,
                interesting and authentic cafes, and also, the hospitality of
                the locals.</p><p>EXIT festival, known for its incredible atmosphere,
                one of the best Dance Arenas in the world and unique location,
                offers visitors the most exciting, versatile summer adventure.
                During 4 days there are from 150 to 200 000 people, of which
                there are at least 23 000 foreign tourists and 7000 visitors
                from the Balkans.</p>]]>
        </content>
    </layout>
    <layout type="img-set" subtype="4b">
        <img isImg="img" size="large">
            <tag>exit-2014</tag>
            <count>09.png</count>
            <advert>
                <tag>tuborg</tag>
            </advert>
        </img>
    </layout>
    <layout type="read-set">
        <content>
            <![CDATA[<h3>The State of Exit Foundation</h3><p><a href="http://fondacija.exitfest.org/">The
                State of Exit Foundation</a> was founded in 2010 in Novi Sad.
                Its main goal is helping young citizens of Novi Sad to gain new
                academic experiences through financing and co-financing their
                scholarships and academic projects. The foundation supports student
                efforts to catch up with advanced scientific research trends
                and high professional standards at the international level in
                science, culture and sports.</p><p>An individual Foundation Scholarship
                Program began in 2010. In cooperation with the University of
                Novi Sad, the Foundation developed a program of scholarships
                for individual students, a program to support individual students’
                projects, as well as student organizations, while it includes
                regular student population in the community and Exit Festival’s
                youth campaigns.</p><p>Since 2013, Exit has a goal to participate
                in mobilizing current opinion and deciding on two areas it has
                been known for: destination branding and youth development. State
                of Exit Foundation dedicates its work to key topics in social
                involvement: national branding, regional connection through creative
                industries, as well as promoting positive examples to the youth.
                It has organized REBRANDING SERBIA conference in Novi Sad in
                July 2013, as well as the Creative Industries Conference (KKIS)
                held in Belgrade on February 2014.</p>]]>
        </content>
    </layout>
</layouts>
