<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<articles>
    <article imgLayout="wide" color="sunset">
		<url>lindsay-lohan-sues-gta-5</url>
        <tag>gta-5</tag>
        <count>02-main.png</count>
        <subtype>news</subtype>
        <title>Lindsay Lohan sues Grand Theft Auto 5 creators for allegedly using
            her likeness</title>
        <content>
            <![CDATA[<p>Actress Lindsay Lohan has reportedly made good on threats
                to sue the developer of <i>Grand Theft Auto 5</i> over claims
                that her likeness is used in the game. <a href="http://bigstory.ap.org/article/lohan-sues-over-grand-theft-auto-v-game">The
                Associated Press</a> reports that Lohan's legal team filed a
                lawsuit in a Manhattan court that alleges Take-Two Interactive
                and Rockstar Games based the character Lacey Jonas on the actress,
                who has starred in <i>Herbie Fully Loaded</i> and <i>The Canyons</i>.
                The developer "incorporated her image, likeness, clothing, outfits,
                [Lohan's] clothing line products, ensemble in the form of hats,
                hair style, sunglasses" and the jean shorts worn by Lohan without
                her permission, <a href="http://www.nydailynews.com/entertainment/gossip/lindsay-lohan-sues-makers-grand-theft-auto-article-1.1852017">according
                to the complaint</a>.</p>]]>
        </content>
    </article>
    <article isQ="q" qImg="boo.png" qOffset="offset">
        <author>Boo</author>
        <title>Boo!</title>
    </article>
    <article imgLayout="small">
		<url>xbox-behind-ps4</url>
        <tag>xbox-behind-ps4</tag>
        <count>01-main.png</count>
        <subtype>feature</subtype>
        <title>Xbox One is languishing behind PS4 – what can Microsoft do to
            put the Xbox brand back on top?</title>
        <symbols>400</symbols>
        <content>
            <![CDATA[<p>The party, if there was one at all, was shortlived. News
                that UK sales of Xbox One had surged 96 per cent in the week
                of Titanfall’s release, with seven out of every ten consoles
                sold alongside Respawn’s multiplayer shooter, should have set
                champagne corks popping in Microsoft’s Redmond HQ. Any suggestion
                that this was the turning point for Xbox One’s fortunes, however,
                was quickly shot down by news that UK sales of PS4 had risen
                by 72 per cent in the same seven-day period. Yet Sony’s boost
                was not driven by the long-awaited arrival of a platform-exclusive
                game release – that would come a week later, when Infamous: Second
                Son saw hardware sales more than double – but by retailers finally
                having enough stock to meet demand. Sony can’t make its new console
                fast enough, while Microsoft’s lies readily available on store
                shelves.</p>]]>
        </content>
    </article>
    <article isQ="q" qImg="minsc.png">
        <author>Minsc</author>
        <title>See battle Boo... RUN Boo RUN!</title>
    </article>
</articles>
