<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<layouts>
    <layout type="read-set">
        <left>
            <article imgLayout="tall" hideInfo="hide">
                <tag>gta-5</tag>
                <subtype>info</subtype>
                <info box="ps4">
                    <bg>Велико Крадене на Коли 5</bg>
                    <en>Grand Theft Auto 5</en>
                    <platform>
                        <tag>Win</tag>
                        <tag>PS4</tag>
                        <tag>One</tag>
                        <tag>PS3</tag>
                        <tag>360</tag>
                    </platform>
                    <publisher>Rockstar Games</publisher>
                    <developer>Rockstar North</developer>
                    <eu>17 Септември 2013</eu>
					<usa>17 Септември 2013</usa>
                </info>
				<advert>
					<button>Купи Играта</button>
					<tag>pulsar</tag>
				</advert>
                <content>
                    <![CDATA[<p>Разработена от създателите на серията Rockstar
                        North, Grand Theft Auto V е най-голямото и най-амбициозното
                        заглавие в поредицата към днешна дата. Развиваща се в
                        обширния град Лос Сантос (Los Santos) и околностите му,
                        Grand Theft Auto V ви дава свят с неповторими мащаби
                        и детайли, кипящ от живот – от високите планински върхове
                        до дълбините на океана.</p>]]>
                </content>
            </article>
        </left>
        <right>
            <article titleSize="big" imgLayout="tall">
				<url>gta-5</url>
                <tag>gta-5</tag>
                <count>01-main.png</count>
                <subtype>review</subtype>
                <title>Велико Краденe на Коли 5</title>
                <symbols>516</symbols>
                <content>
                    <![CDATA[<p>If first impressions count, Grand Theft Auto
                        V is in trouble. This is a miserable opening, breaking
                        the series tradition of dropping you into a fast car
                        in a beautiful city, instead kicking off in a snow-driven
                        town in the American Midwest with a flashback heist.
                        The first thing you do is hold up on the left analogue
                        stick for two seconds before control is snatched away
                        from you. Behind the wheel of a car, you spin out on
                        icy roads. As a way of beginning a story it makes sense,
                        but it’s a lacklustre way to open a videogame. Thankfully,
                        within half an hour we’ve got one car stuck on a fire
                        hydrant, flipped another over into the path of an oncoming
                        train, and taken a third on a police chase out of the
                        city and made our escape on a jetski. Normal service
                        is resumed. And it just gets better from there.</p>]]>
                </content>
                <url>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wRipBOQl95o</url>
            </article>
        </right>
        <content>
            <![CDATA[<h2>Lindsay Lohan sues Grand Theft Auto 5 creators for allegedly
                using her likeness</h2>]]>
        </content>
    </layout>
    <layout type="img-set">
        <img isImg="img" size="large">
            <tag>gta-5</tag>
            <count>01-960.png</count>
        </img>
    </layout>
    <layout type="read-set">
        <content>
            <![CDATA[<p>Actress Lindsay Lohan has reportedly made good on threats
                to sue the developer of <i>Grand Theft Auto 5</i> over claims
                that her likeness is used in the game.</p><p><a href="http://bigstory.ap.org/article/lohan-sues-over-grand-theft-auto-v-game">The
                Associated Press</a> reports that Lohan's legal team filed a
                lawsuit in a Manhattan court that alleges Take-Two Interactive
                and Rockstar Games based the character Lacey Jonas on the
                actress, who has starred in <i>Herbie Fully Loaded</i> and <i>The
                Canyons</i>.</p><p>The developer "incorporated her image, likeness,
                clothing, outfits, [Lohan's] clothing line products, ensemble
                in the form of hats, hair style, sunglasses" and the jean shorts
                worn by Lohan without her permission, <a href="http://www.nydailynews.com/entertainment/gossip/lindsay-lohan-sues-makers-grand-theft-auto-article-1.1852017">according
                to the complaint</a>.</p>]]>
        </content>
    </layout>
    <layout type="img-set">
        <left>
            <article isQ="q" qImg="michael.png">
                <author>Michael</author>
                <title>You are what hipsters aspire to be. You, Trevor, are the
                    proto-hipster.</title>
            </article>
        </left>
		<img isImg="img" size="medium">
            <tag>gta-5</tag>
            <count>02-640.png</count>
            <pointer>Ляво</pointer>
            <content>
                <![CDATA[Here's Lacey Jonas as she appears in-game.]]>
            </content>
        </img>
    </layout>
    <layout type="read-set">
        <right>
            <article isQ="q" qImg="trevor.png">
                <author>Trevor</author>
                <title>I don’t know what you’re talking about. I don’t agree
                    with what you’re saying. You’re talking bullshit and you’re
                    trying to wind me up. But I’m very, very angry and I want
                    this conversation to stop right away.</title>
            </article>
        </right>
        <content>
            <![CDATA[<p>The suit also alleges that the in-game hotel Gentry Manor,
                based on West Hollywood hotel Chateau Marmont, is associated
                with Lohan, as she formerly resided there.</p><p>In <i><a href="#">Grand
                Theft Auto 5</a></i>, players can encounter Lacey Jonas in a
                mission in which they must escort her to escape the paparazzi.
                Her in-game dialogue portrays her as a famous Vinewood actress
                with an eating disorder.</p><p><i>GTA 5</i> was released for
                PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360 on Sept. 17, 2013. The game will <a
                href="#" sl-processed="1">come to PlayStation 4, Windows PC and
                Xbox One</a> later this year.</p>]]>
        </content>
    </layout>
    <layout type="video-set" priority="high">
        <left>
            <article isQ="q" qImg="michael.png">
                <author>Michael</author>
                <title>Hipster.</title>
            </article>
        </left>
		<article imgLayout="large" priority="high" isVideo="video" player="1">
            <tag>gta-5</tag>
            <count>04-main.png</count>
            <subtype>video</subtype>
            <title>Grand Theft Auto V: Coming for PlayStation 4, Xbox One and
                PC this fall</title>
            <url>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3DBrG2YjqQA</url>
        </article>
        <article imgLayout="small" priority="high" isVideo="video" player="1">
            <tag>gta-5</tag>
            <count>03-main.png</count>
            <subtype>video</subtype>
            <title>Grand Theft Auto V: Official gameplay video</title>
            <url>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=N-xHcvug3WI</url>
        </article>
        <article imgLayout="small" priority="high" isVideo="video" isLast="last" player="1">
            <tag>gta-5</tag>
            <count>05-main.png</count>
            <subtype>video</subtype>
            <title>GTA Online: "I'm Not a Hipster" live stream</title>
            <url>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=obEsBJ6Eb8k</url>
        </article>
    </layout>
    <layout type="article-set" subtype="small-set-caret-left" priority="medium">
		<left valign="bottom">
            <article isQ="q" qImg="michael.png">
                <author>Michael</author>
                <title>I’ve made my point. I’m not a sadist.</title>
            </article>
        </left>
		<right>
            <article isQ="q" qImg="trevor.png">
                <author>Trevor</author>
                <title>F*ck you! F*ck you, Michael! Say it again!</title>
            </article>
        </right>
        <article titleSize="big" imgLayout="tall" isCaret="caret">
            <tag>red-dead-redemption</tag>
            <count>01-main.png</count>
            <subtype>feature</subtype>
            <title>Time Extend: Red Dead Redemption</title>
            <content>
                <![CDATA[<p>The myth of the old west is a perfect fit for Rockstar.
                    Here’s a genre of cinema with game-like themes, a setting
                    that lends itself easily to the open-world treatment, and
                    one that naturally supports the subjects that have become
                    dominant in Dan Houser’s writing as it’s matured. The old
                    west offers a particular vision of masculinity in a time
                    of crisis, and deals in the collision between the individual
                    and society. It is also an opportunity to diagnose the state
                    of life in modern America by exploring the fable of the nation’s
                    creation.</p>]]>
            </content>
        </article>
        <article imgLayout="small">
            <tag>gta-5</tag>
            <count>07-main.png</count>
            <subtype>feature</subtype>
            <title>Still Playing: GTA 5 – forget the killing sprees and find
                beauty in a digital rambling holiday</title>
            <content>
                <![CDATA[<p>Collectibles may not ruin games, but they don’t exactly
                    help. They’re the tedious make-work at the heart of modern
                    game design that substitutes padding for content, the taunting
                    fraction lurking in some number-ish recess of the pause screen
                    showing you how little you’ve actually achieved. Very few
                    are as tedious as GTAIV’s pigeons. They distort progress
                    – thought you were only 30 per cent of the way through the
                    story? Tough luck sir, the remaining 70 per cent is killing
                    200 pigeons – and hold players in contempt, asking them to
                    exterminate a city-full of grey, stub-legged sky-rats for
                    no reason and scant reward. In a Saints Row game, you might
                    get away with arguing that this was parody; with GTAIV’s
                    dour tone, it just felt like sadism – or worse, as if Rockstar
                    didn’t care.</p>]]>
            </content>
        </article>
        <article imgLayout="small">
            <tag>gta-5</tag>
            <count>06-main.png</count>
            <subtype>feature</subtype>
            <title>Revisiting GTA 5’s Los Santos, a mirror LA that’s the perfect
                match for Rockstar’s lampooning eye</title>
            <content>
                <![CDATA[<p>The French novelist Henry De Montherlant wrote, “Happiness
                    writes in white ink on a white page.” His argument was that,
                    from Charles Dickens to Ian McEwan, only fiction’s tragedies,
                    trials, aberrations and villains lodge in the mind; the good
                    guys and the good things that happen to them are, a few notable
                    exceptions aside, forgettable. It’s a belief that’s seemingly
                    characterised the work of Rockstar North, the developer of
                    the Grand Theft Auto series, whose rogues’ gallery of gangsters,
                    mobsters and tricksters has smeared dark stories across our
                    screens for the past 17 years. Our protagonists lie and cheat
                    for every last dollar, grinding into the sand the heads of
                    those they clamber over, and, in doing so, imprinting themselves
                    in our memories.</p>]]>
            </content>
        </article>
    </layout>
</layouts>
