<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<layouts>
    <layout type="read-set">
        <content>
            <![CDATA[<h2>Костенурките Нинджа</h2>]]>
        </content>
    </layout>
    <layout type="img-set">
        <img isImg="img" size="large" playVideo="video" player="1">
			<url>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wRipBOQl95o</url>
            <tag>ninja-turtles-2014</tag>
            <count>01-1920.png</count>
        </img>
    </layout>
    <layout type="read-set">
        <content>
            <![CDATA[<p>Нова филмова адаптация по култовата анимационна поредица
                от детството ни. Режисирана от Джонатан Либесман, "дарил" ни
                с филми като Battle L.A. и Wrath of the Titans. Продукцията е
                под патронажа на Майкъл Бей. Костенурките имат... носове. И за
                да кажем все пак нещо хубаво - Меган Фокс ще играе Ейприл О'Нийл.
                А и честно казано очаквахме нещата да изглеждат далеч по-зле
                от показаното. Гледай и прецени.</p>]]>
        </content>
    </layout>
    <layout type="video-set" priority="high">
		<article imgLayout="large" priority="high" isVideo="video" player="1">
            <tag>gta-5</tag>
            <count>04-main.png</count>
            <subtype>video</subtype>
            <title>Grand Theft Auto V: Coming for PlayStation 4, Xbox One and
                PC this fall</title>
            <url>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3DBrG2YjqQA</url>
        </article>
        <article imgLayout="small" priority="high" isVideo="video" player="1">
            <tag>gta-5</tag>
            <count>03-main.png</count>
            <subtype>video</subtype>
            <title>Grand Theft Auto V: Official gameplay video</title>
            <url>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=N-xHcvug3WI</url>
        </article>
        <article imgLayout="small" priority="high" isVideo="video" isLast="last" player="1">
            <tag>gta-5</tag>
            <count>05-main.png</count>
            <subtype>video</subtype>
            <title>GTA Online: "I'm Not a Hipster" live stream</title>
            <url>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=obEsBJ6Eb8k</url>
        </article>
    </layout>
    <layout type="article-set" subtype="small-set-caret-left" priority="medium">
        <article titleSize="big" imgLayout="tall" isCaret="caret">
            <tag>red-dead-redemption</tag>
            <count>01-main.png</count>
            <subtype>feature</subtype>
            <title>Time Extend: Red Dead Redemption</title>
            <content>
                <![CDATA[<p>The myth of the old west is a perfect fit for Rockstar.
                    Here’s a genre of cinema with game-like themes, a setting
                    that lends itself easily to the open-world treatment, and
                    one that naturally supports the subjects that have become
                    dominant in Dan Houser’s writing as it’s matured. The old
                    west offers a particular vision of masculinity in a time
                    of crisis, and deals in the collision between the individual
                    and society. It is also an opportunity to diagnose the state
                    of life in modern America by exploring the fable of the nation’s
                    creation.</p>]]>
            </content>
        </article>
        <article imgLayout="small">
            <tag>gta-5</tag>
            <count>02-main.png</count>
            <subtype>feature</subtype>
            <title>Still Playing: GTA 5 – forget the killing sprees and find
                beauty in a digital rambling holiday</title>
            <content>
                <![CDATA[<p>Collectibles may not ruin games, but they don’t exactly
                    help. They’re the tedious make-work at the heart of modern
                    game design that substitutes padding for content, the taunting
                    fraction lurking in some number-ish recess of the pause screen
                    showing you how little you’ve actually achieved. Very few
                    are as tedious as GTAIV’s pigeons. They distort progress
                    – thought you were only 30 per cent of the way through the
                    story? Tough luck sir, the remaining 70 per cent is killing
                    200 pigeons – and hold players in contempt, asking them to
                    exterminate a city-full of grey, stub-legged sky-rats for
                    no reason and scant reward. In a Saints Row game, you might
                    get away with arguing that this was parody; with GTAIV’s
                    dour tone, it just felt like sadism – or worse, as if Rockstar
                    didn’t care.</p>]]>
            </content>
        </article>
        <article imgLayout="small">
            <tag>gta-5</tag>
            <count>06-main.png</count>
            <subtype>feature</subtype>
            <title>Revisiting GTA 5’s Los Santos, a mirror LA that’s the perfect
                match for Rockstar’s lampooning eye</title>
            <content>
                <![CDATA[<p>The French novelist Henry De Montherlant wrote, “Happiness
                    writes in white ink on a white page.” His argument was that,
                    from Charles Dickens to Ian McEwan, only fiction’s tragedies,
                    trials, aberrations and villains lodge in the mind; the good
                    guys and the good things that happen to them are, a few notable
                    exceptions aside, forgettable. It’s a belief that’s seemingly
                    characterised the work of Rockstar North, the developer of
                    the Grand Theft Auto series, whose rogues’ gallery of gangsters,
                    mobsters and tricksters has smeared dark stories across our
                    screens for the past 17 years. Our protagonists lie and cheat
                    for every last dollar, grinding into the sand the heads of
                    those they clamber over, and, in doing so, imprinting themselves
                    in our memories.</p>]]>
            </content>
        </article>
    </layout>
</layouts>
